Well, here at Yakanta Idol, we have a section called "My 3 major elements".
Last time we had Sakura-san present them!
This time, I'd like to talk about the other three members of the team from your point of view.
The other three, well, we've been working together for two teams already.
I'm sure you know many aspects of them.
First of all, what kind of person is Haruna Takamoto, the youngest member of the team?
Well, Haru, she is all-around person.
Well, I think her fans know that.
She's a really accomplished girl, and one thing I especially admire about her is that she's really good at remembering people's faces and names.
She's really good at remembering people's faces and names.
She's really, really good.
I mean, she's really good at remembering the faces and names of the staff and the fans.
And of course, fans.
I have a lot of opportunities to meet so many people.
I've seen his face before, but I don't know what his name is.
Or, on the other hand, "I've seen this person's face before, but I don't remember his name.
I can't help but come up with questions like, "Who is this person?
And if there is a fan whose name is a bit similar to mine...
I often wonder which one is which.
But in the spring, I often meet staff members whom I haven't seen for a long time, and they say, "Oh, it's been a long time.
I say, "Ah, it's been a long time, that time, that time..." and then they spread out far away.
And then they spread out far and wide.
That's really an amazing part.
I often witness this scene.
When we work with new people, especially when it's the first time to work with them...
Super Tasty Lang Ineasy Positive Exciting Soul from Nagaya Team Sharts
We always greet each other in the usual way.
On the other hand, when we meet for the first time in a while On the other hand, I haven't seen you in a while.
For example, we met before we met each other, and we haven't seen each other in a while.
I would do it again.
But to do it again after seeing each other for a while...
I feel like I've been forgotten by the staff.
So, if it's the second time I've seen you, I'll say
I really want to say, "Oh, it's been a while," but
But there are moments when I feel a little lost.
Yes, that's true.
And at that moment, the person who takes the initiative in greeting you is
Honoka Akimoto.
She says, "We're going to do it this way.
That's right.
But at the moment when we are on the verge of saying it or not
The moment when we should do it.
A faint flicker of recognition.
And then the second time you do it.
I often see him do that.
But really Spring is
She's really amazing in that aspect, as well as her memory.
And her memory, too.
I'm sure Akimoto-san really appreciates that.
I see.
Akimoto-san is also not very good at remembering people's names and faces.
It's a cute side of her.
You know a lot about people.
Yes, I do.
She also knows when to say hello to you.There was also the timing of the greeting to Mr. Akimoto.
And the timing of that and so on.
Honoka-chan, Honoka-chan, super tough.
Super tough is what you always say to me in the spring.
Oh, you mean Mr. Sakamoto.
Even to that point.
That's right.
You tell me I'm super tough.
I think so.
I think that's true.
Spring is really one of the things I admire about him, especially that part.
Also, she's really cute, isn't she?
Simply so.
No matter how tough the moment is.
She tries to enjoy everything.
She's really good at putting a positive spin on things.
When I'm with her
I feel like we're having fun too.
Haru is really indispensable to us.
She is very important to us.
Yes, sir.
What kind of person is Yuzuki Daikoku?
Yuzuki Daikoku is...
Yuzuki also has a very good memory.
About a certain genre...
What is it?What is it?
I have a very good memory for episodic memories.
It's amazing.
I can't even remember Bameri.
Did it happen a little bit at a time?
No, no, no.
Sometimes I'm off by 0.25 or something.
Yes, sir.
Why do you remember that? I'm not sure why you remember that.
For example, I can say a line from a play I did a few years ago.
If I put something like that in once and put it on stage...
I'm the type of person who gets deleted immediately.
I'm the type of person who gets deleted as soon as I say something like that.
But with Yuzuki, there were lines like that.
Songs I covered in the past
or remembering the choreography of songs we covered in the past.
She is really good at bringing back memories from the past.
When we talk about memories
Yuzuki is the only one who remembers so much.
and the rest of the members remember that? It's just an everyday occurrence.
It's an everyday occurrence.
Misaki-san has a talk show about once every two months.
Episodic talks are very important.
Is that so?
I'm sure they're very helpful.
Very much so.
Do you watch the talk show?
Yes, I do. Yes, sir.
Because we do a lot of that in Nagoya.
Yes, everyone in Nagoya.
There's that twitterer, too.
Next to him.
Is that so? I'll pay closer attention.
I'll pay a little more attention.
After talking with Yuzuki...
I remember that I had a chance to talk with Yuzuki.
Yes, that's right.
Yes, I'm the backstage manager.
That word really fits you, doesn't it?
Yes.
Yes, it does.
And Yuzuki?
I want to show everyone.
The episode talk is amazing.
You've been doing a webcast called Yuzuki's Room.
You've been making great use of that, haven't you?
Yes.
And because of that show, Yuzuki has more opportunities
Yuzuki has more chances to get involved with her juniors.
Like the other day at the localism show.
I thought Yuzuki was the chairman of the show.
There were so many junior members around him.
They were talking a lot.
I wondered when she had become such a big sister.
I was wondering when she became such a big sister. I was a little surprised to see Yuzuki become a big sister.
I was surprised to see Yuzuki become a big sister before I knew it.
She's so cool!
Today, we heard about the personalities of Mr. Sakamoto and Mr. Omura.
Tomorrow, we will record a lot of Akimoto-san's songs.
Oshimen, isn't that right?
Yes, please feel the good things about oshimen!
There are so many!
Oh!
I'm looking forward to tomorrow! Thank you very much for today!
Thank you very much!